mytreo.net 2004-12-04

# mytreo.net - Privacy Notice

How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page of the site. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the mytreo.net website. On some pages, you required to register to receive full website functioanlity. The types of personal information collected upon registration are: 

Name   
Email address 

On some pages, you can submit further information about yourself in order to receive a product or item by mail. For example, if you enter into a competition online and would like to be eligible to receive the prize you will need to submit your address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name   
Address   
Phone Number 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when registering only to verify your application for membership. We do not share this information with outside parties. 

We use the information you provide about yourself when receiving an item only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that shipment. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as exclusive members offers on Treo related products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you specifically request that it should be. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access and edit all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to the site and viewing your profile in the forum page. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access, making corrections, or resetting passwords. 

Please help us by ensuring your registered email address is up-to-date and valid. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at forumadmin@mytreo.net.
